

570.447.4057

WilCoYonkin@me.com

ACCOUNT MANAGER | CLIENT SUCCESS MANAGER

With a comprehensive background in technology and a natural gift for connection and communication, I've bridged the gap between complex problems and client-based solutions for over 5 years. My experience ranges from problem solving for C-suite stakeholders to teaching JavaScript to students. I'm a well-rounded, client-centric, team player that can translate intricate technical jargon into palatable explanations and actions.

EXPERIENCE

Code Ninjas

CODE INSTRUCTOR

September 2023 - August 2024

- Guided learners to aid understanding and knowledge of technology and coding concepts
- Taught JavaScript, Python, and C++ fundamentals using Impact, Microsoft MakeCode, and Unity
- Customized and supplemented curricular materials to ensure knowledge transfer and growth
- Debugged student code projects using browser developer tools and collaborative troubleshooting
- Leveraged educator background to inspire learners' confidence in technology, math, and science

PICS ITECH

CLIENT ACCOUNT MANAGER

October 2021 - May 2022

- Managed CRM account data and quickly resolved service tickets queue for 60+ clients
- Collaborated with clients to understand their business objectives and technical requirements
- Liaised between clients and technical teams, assisting communication and understanding
- Collaborated with internal and external partners to drive projects from onboarding through closure

Apple

TECHNICAL EXPERT

June 2017 - October 2021

- Interpreted customer concerns and delivered appropriate product diagnoses and solutions
- Flexibly rotated through multiple technical specialties and skill sets with ease and confidence
- Translated complex technical insights into understandable and enlightening solutions
- Troubleshot device issues with customers and set appropriate expectations
- Trained new employees on software and hardware troubleshooting and company values

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

AmeriCorps

CORPS MEMBER

February 2014 - May 2016

- Managed programmatic initiatives and outreach strategies for remote cross-functional teams
- Led project development, coordination, and implementation for internal and external teams

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

Full-Stack Engineer Professional Certification, Codecademy 2024
Front End Engineer Professional Certification, Codecademy 2024

Bachelor's Degree Equivalent through Codecademy certifications and professional experience